Man, it's been great. This my first time
really in like in New York, so it's been
it's been a blessing. U I got my wife
with me. Um man, I'm I'm still kind of
feel like I'm dreaming. I gotta get
pinched a little bit. You know what I'm
saying? Uh but no, seriously, it's it's
been great these past couple hours just
knowing that I'm a Buffalo Bill for life
now. Um it's been amazing. Um getting to
know everybody in the building, uh
seeing everything around, it's been
great. Um and then, you know, continuing
to, you know, get embedded into the
program and organization. So, we don't
see a lot of rookies that are already
married, right? A lot of college kids
are not married yet. How what
>> I mean, you got married and you're still
in college. What was that like being
married in college and now you start
your NFL career and you're already you
already got a wife and you know what I
mean,
>> man? It's amazing. You know, like you
know, when you know, you know. You know
what I'm saying? Um, and for me, you
know, just seeing my parents, you know,
have a a loving long-lasting
relationship. They've been together
25 plus years. Um, so that's just what
I've grown around. Um, and then she's
been nothing but amazing to me. Um, you
know, everything she do for me has been
amazing. Um, we always we're best
friends. You know what I'm saying? Um,
and you know, she makes my life a
thousand times easier and that's all I
can ask for. Um, so you know, for me it
was just easy. It was easy to to to say
I want to marry you. Um, and you know,
being in college married is it's cool.
All my teammates, they look at me as as
even though even though I'm probably
younger than them, everybody look at me
as wise as mine. Um, and they come for
me for everything. Um, and they look at
her as a mom, too, cuz she treat them
like they little kids and she takes them
in. Um, it's great though. It keeps you
keeps you focused um, on one goal and
it's amazing. So,
>> why did you find it important?
>> Who's the better athlete?
>> I I say she's the better athlete. You
know what I'm saying? Anything she picks
up, she can do very well. Um, besides
just football. Football is me. You know
what I'm saying? But any other sport,
maybe basketball, I challenge her a
little bit. You know what I'm saying? Um
but she won't she won't admit to that
one. Uh but yeah, I I would definitely
say she's the better athlete.
>> Um the importance of of meeting
everybody here and does that how does
that reflect you as a person and maybe
the excitement that you have had of
arriving here?
>> Uh it means a lot to me. Um I'm a people
person. Um you know the people make the
place. Um and I'm coming from a
organization in Clemson whereas in you
know everything was about family, about
people. Um, and I'm just so glad that
Bill's Mafia is the same way. I come in
here and, you know, I want to introduce
myself to everybody here because if we
all gonna work together, um, I want it
to be a great environment where we can
be we be oursel. Um, that's just how I
roll and that's just what I do and
that's what I stand for. So
>> TJ, first of all, Landon Jackson also,
he was married when he got drafted here,
so he's running mate on defense. You
know, he actually came up here and we
had some of the same questions uh, for
him. your your game, you have
explosiveness, but a lot of it, from
what I've read, is built on power
>> at a little shy of 300 lb. How can that
translate to the NFL and what do you
need to do to make sure that power is
able to go against offensive tackles at
this league?
>> Um, I think it'll translate uh pretty
well. Um, you know, there's some
obviously there's going to be some
learning curves from transition from
college to pros. Um, but I already know
with my mindset, I'm going to work hard
and give it all I got. Um, and I'm going
to lean on, you know, the older vets,
you know, we got Chub and and Greg
Russo, you know, um, and then we got Ed
obviously. I'm going lean on those guys
heavily as possible um just really to
you know get under their wing and just
learn uh quickly so I can help out the
team. So
>> not to recognize that your body type is
very similar to Brad Ch like when you
see a bag like that with a body type
that's similar. I would imagine you want
to kind of like find out what works for
him knowing there's a very good chance
it'll work for you too. You subscribe to
that approach or
>> absolutely. Um and I can't wait to meet
the guys. You know what I'm saying? I
got I got a lot of questions for them.
You know what I'm saying? just how they
treat their body and you know how they
go about things just so I can see if I
can take little nuggets from them
implement it within my regiment and uh
you know uh make it work. So
>> what number will you be wearing and what
was it like when you first took a look
at that uh that that hallway facility
there?
>> Am I allowed to say that right now?
Okay. Am I good to say that?
>> We gonna wait for that. We going to
wait. We going to wait for I'm I'mma let
them You know what I'm saying? I'm I'mma
allow I'mma allow them to do that. You
know what I'm saying? Um, but man, uh,
what was your your second part of that
question? I'm sorry.
>> Touring the facilities and you see the
the weight room. Uh, you know, what was
what was what was it like taking a tour
of that? Uh,
>> oh man, I'm I'm I'm going to put
emphasis on this weight room. It was
unbelievable. I know I'm coming from
Clemson. We had a great weight room, but
man, the weight room is just it was
crazy. It was very open, man. It just
spacious. I wanted I wanted to bench
press right then and there. You know
what I'm saying? Uh, man, I loved it.
Um, those are the areas you I'm going to
spend most of my time in, uh, getting
better. So, uh, just to see it as
beautiful as that, it's been great.
Facility has been great, you know, and I
can't wait to see the new stadium. Um,
that'll be unbelievable. I've seen
little Instagram clips of it and how it
was built, like the process. So, it's
pretty cool.
>> Bean said that they had a they somebody
here on staff who was with Clemson or I
don't know, maybe you know the name. I
don't I forget who it was, but is very
familiar with the Clemson program. He's
here on staff, knows how they operate.
What is what was your communication like
maybe through the season even with
anybody on the Bills knowing kind of you
had people there that kind of knew about
each other? Did really just start in the
pre-draft process?
>> Um Keith Jennings is who you're talking
about. I call him Jug Head, man. I love
Jug Head. Um we've had a great
relationship since I got to college, you
know, and I'm I'm a big on improvement.
So I've always asked like are like what
you see that I can improve in when he
watching my tape and things like that.
We've gone back and forth with that. You
know what I'm saying? Um just trying to
understand where I can get better. Um,
and you know, him just just being a
Clemson guy, you know, he's always
looking out for me. He always, uh, you
know what I'm saying? Make sure I'm on
top of my game, make sure I'm a good
person and stuff still. Um, and he's
always rooting for me regardless of
what's going on through my ups and
downs. Um, and I appreciate him a lot.
And I'm just super excited that, you
know, I get to get in the building with
him, spend a lot of time with him, him
being an alumni as well from Clemson.
Um, it's amazing. So,
>> have you talked to Shaq Lawson at all?
He had uh he had uh tweeted uh uh
excitement about your arrival in Buffalo
after playing here many years.
>> I got to hit the guy up. You know what
I'm saying? That's my that's my dog,
man. Uh and his his younger brother, J,
man. I love him to death. We we played
three years together, man. I'll do
anything for him. The Lawson family in
general, they they're great people. Um
they're Clemson people. U man through
and through. And if y'all know Shaq, you
hear him before you see him in the
building. You know what I'm saying?
>> And that but that's that's him though.
That's him though. That's real
authentic. You know what I'm saying? And
and that's one thing I appreciate, you
know what I'm saying, about about Shaq.
He going to keep it real regardless of
what's going on. Um, man, so I'm
definitely going to hit him up after
this one.
>> Talk about Davos Sweeney and how, you
know, he prepared you for this process,
>> man. Coach Sweeney, uh, man, I love him
to death. First of all, he kept it real
with me. You know what I'm saying? I
didn't have uh the greatest year that
that people would wanted me to have. Um,
but at the same time, I put a lot of
good things on tape and he he kept it
real. said, "If this is what you feel,
this how you feel about leaving and you
ready, just know that you got you going
to have to prepare and have a great a
great spring." Um, and he he he
understood I was I was always mentally
wired the right way to do whatever I had
to do. Um, and he was never really
worried about me. Um, you know, he
always shared his insight about the
process and how it would go. Um, and you
know, he was always a lifeline if I had
any questions. Um, and he was always
there to encourage me, always calling,
always making sure I was good when I was
in Cali training. Um, you know, he's
always somebody I can always revert back
to and, you know, call if anything
needed. Um, so I I really appreciate
Coach Sweeney. Uh, it's one of my
favorite people I've ever met. He's
really helped me change my life. So,
>> you talking about putting pain on
people?
>> How are you planning to do that? And how
would you make that effective with the
rest of the defense?
>> I'm running out there and hit somebody.
You know what I'm saying? Look, since I
was four years old, I told my mom I want
to hit somebody and she threw me in
football. Um, always been physical,
always been violent. That's just how I
play the game. I mean, it's just I think
that's how the game should be played.
Um, so for me, I'mma fly around, fly to
run to the ball, and we're going to hit
people. We're going to put pads on pads.
You know what I'm saying? That's how the
game needs to be played.
>> Did you see that your quarterback
teammate was just drafted by your
division rival now, the Jets?
>> Kade.
>> Yeah, just showed me that. And Kade,
when you see this, man, look, if I get a
chance to play you and you out there
throwing that rock, it ain't no ain't no
practice now. You ain't got no purple
jerseys on. I I don't got to ease up no
more. I'm going run full speed through
you. You know what I'm saying?
Obviously, I'm I'mma land with my hands
on the ground so we don't get fined. You
know what I'm saying? We going we going
to play within the parameters. Uh but
man, I'm super excited for him, man.
He's a hard worker. Unbelievable guy. Uh
he going to come in right away, try to,
you know what I'm saying, be a leader as
much as possible. I mean, I'm super
excited to see how his career pan out.
Uh obviously, they got Gino Smith there,
so that'd be great for him to learn
behind him, um and get things going. So,
I'm super excited for him. TJ, I would
imagine, you know, when you get drafted,
you've got all of these different
thoughts and emotions that are going
through your head now that you've had a
little bit of time. I guess what is the
thought about landing in Buffalo and
what have you been thinking about since
you got the call last night?
>> That I'm going to Buffalo and like I I
couldn't believe it. You know what I'm
saying? Like you guys are are winners.
You guys constantly win. You always find
a way and a great culture. I always see
crazy things about how the fans support
and doing whatever it takes. Um, and I
love that. That's what I've been around
my entire football career. Um, and just
to be a part of that now, it's amazing
and I really can't wait to, you know,
for to be embedded in more and the fans
know who I am. So,
>> I know you didn't get any sleep last
night, but it's like what it going to be
like, you know, you be able to get the
ball back to Josh Allen.
>> It's going to be amazing. I can't wait
to meet him. You know what I'm saying?
Uh when we found out we was going to the
Bills, I had there was a couple Bills
fans in the background who uh they
probably crying like they won the Super
Bowl uh knowing I was going here. But
man, I I can't wait. I'm going do
whatever it takes to, you know, give him
the ball back much as possible so he can
go win some games. So
>> you lined up against Jude Bowie last
season, Clemson versus Boston College.
The girls just selected him not too long
ago. Have you talked with him at all?
>> I ain't talked to him yet, but man, I'm
excited. You know what I'm saying? We're
going to get more work in. Uh he's a
great player. Um, I'm super happy for
him and his family. You know what I'm
saying? I hope he enjoy this moment. Uh,
cuz we'll be up here soon. So, I know
he's ready to work. I'm ready to work.
Let's get to it.
>> IGB today from Ohio State. What was that
conversation like?
>> That was dope, man. We really just
shared experience about, you know, how
we was waiting for the call and how we
excited to be here. U, we excited to
win. Um, I got his phone number. So, we
g we locked in now. You know what I'm
saying? I'm going to spend as much time.
I'll help him however he needs it. Um,
and I know he'll help me.